Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXIV. LOCAL LODGES
  - Sub-Series 235-1303. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1303, Tie Plant Lodge, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1951-1952 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      July 9, 1951-July 1, 1952. Consolidated with Lodge No. 251, Albuquerque, New Mexico, effective April 1, 1952
    - Lodge No. 1303, Mexico Lodge, Mexico, Missouri, 1935-1936 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      October 9, 1935-January 10, 1936. Disbanded, effective December 21, 1935
  - Sub-Series 235-1307. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1307, Sherbrooke Lodge, Sherbrooke, Quebec, Canada, 1922-1924 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      November 27, 1922-June 11, 1924. Abandoned 1924?
  - Sub-Series 235-1309. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1309, Grand Haven Lodge, Long Island City, New York, 1951-1956 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      October 29, 1951-June 12, 1956. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1268, New York, New York, effective January 1, 1956
  - Sub-Series 235-1311. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1311, Taunton, Massachusetts, 1932-1958 (Box 143, Folder 13)
      October 6, 1932-July 25, 1958. Consolidated with Lodge No. 143, Boston, Massachusetts, effective July 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-1313. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1313, Youngstown Lodge, Youngstown, Ohio, 1951-1960 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      November 19, 1951-July 22, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 451, Youngstown, Ohio and Lodge No. 1228, Ashtabula, Ohio, effective April 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 1313, Moncton Lodge, Moncton, New Brunswick, Canada, 1922 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      January 25, 1922-February 3, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1315. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1315, Pacific Electric Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1959-1960 (Box 143, Folder 15)
      October 22, 1959-September 28, 1960. Subject: "Appeal Robert J. Daigle paying the sum of $62.90 dues from November 1957 to May 1959 and the sum of $9.00 dues for November and December 1959 to Pacific Electric Lodge No. 1315 under Protest"
    - Lodge No. 1315, Pacific Electric Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1960-1962 (Box 143, Folder 16)
      May 3, 1960-December 18, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 1315, Pacific Electric Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1956-1959 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      October 22, 1956-December 7, 1959.
    - Lodge No. 1315, Pacific Electric Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1951-1957 (Box 143, Folder 18)
      November 19, 1951-September 30, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-1318. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1318, Cerro Gordo Lodge, Mason City, Iowa, 1921-1922 (Box 143, Folder 19)
      February 1, 1921-October 23, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1319. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1319, M. & N. A. Lodge, Harrison, Arkansas, 1921-1923 (Box 143, Folder 20)
      December 8, 1921-March 21, 1923. Disbanded?
  - Sub-Series 235-1320. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1320, Ayearst Lodge, Muskegon, Michigan, 1927-1962 (Box 143, Folder 21)
      October 18, 1927-November 19, 1962. Formerly Pere Marquette Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 810, Ludington, Michigan, effective January 1, 1962
    - Lodge No. 1320, Central of Georgia Lodge, Albany, Georgia, 1922 (Box 143, Folder 21)
      March 8-23, 1922. Disbanded, effective February 27, 1922
  - Sub-Series 235-1321. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1321, Passumpsic Lodge, St. Johnsbury, Vermont, 1926-1930 (Box 143, Folder 22)
      December 31, 1926-December 18, 1930. Disbanded?
  - Sub-Series 235-1323. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1323, Delaware Lodge, Wilmington, Delaware, 1945-1960 (Box 143, Folder 23)
      October 1, 1945-November 22, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 518, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, effective October 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 1323, Carbondale, Pennsylvania, 1921 (Box 143, Folder 23)
      1921 February, 18
  - Sub-Series 235-1325. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1325, Clarence Hosch Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1952-1968 (Box 143, Folder 24)
      March 28, 1952-April 19, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1270, St. Louis, Missouri, effective April 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1326. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1326, Victory Lodge, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1921-1962 (Box 143, Folder 25)
      December 9, 1921-October 10, 1962. Disbanded, effective June 30, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1331. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1331, Monroe Lodge, Rochester, New York, 1921-1967 (Box 143, Folder 26)
      December 30, 1921-February 7, 1967. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1215, Rochester, New York, effective January 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1332. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1332, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, 1948 (Box 143, Folder 27)
      1948 December 22. Consolidated with Lodge No. 692, Marion, Iowa, effective December 22, 1948
  - Sub-Series 235-1333. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1333, Steel Valley Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1952-1962 (Box 143, Folder 28)
      September 8, 1952-December 10, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 1333, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1922-1923 (Box 143, Folder 28)
      June 22, 1922-April 24, 1923. Suspended, effective March 31, 1923
  - Sub-Series 235-1335. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1335, Cedar Central Lodge, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, 1931-1960 (Box 143, Folder 29)
      January 20, 1931-October 21, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 954, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, effective October 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1336. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1336, Cornbelt Lodge, Oelwein, Iowa, 1921-1968 (Box 143, Folder 30)
      September 9, 1921-October 1, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. Lodge No. 120, Chicago, Illinois; Lodge No. 369, Boone, Iowa; Lodge No. 679, Chicago, Illinois; Lodge No. 863, Chicago, Illinois; Lodge No. 1163, Chicago, Illinois; Lodge No. 1296, Omaha, Nebraska; and Lodge No. 1480, Cedar Rapids, Iowa; effective October 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1339. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1339, James Bowden Lodge, Alexandria, Virginia, 1953-1961 (Box 143, Folder 31)
      March 30, 1953-January 24, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1795, Richmond, Virginia, effective January 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 1339, White Plains, New York, 1933 (Box 143, Folder 31)
      1933 January 18. Suspended, effective January 18, 1933
  - Sub-Series 235-1340. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1340, Temples Lodge, Augusta, Georgia, 1953-1957 (Box 143, Folder 32)
      April 6, 1953-January 24, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 323, Macon, Georgia, effective October 1, 1956
    - Lodge No. 1340, Ann Arbor Employees Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1922 (Box 143, Folder 32)
      January 24, 1922-December 7, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1341. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1341, Midwest Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1953-1955 (Box 143, Folder 33)
      April 20, 1953-June 22, 1955. Consolidated with Lodge No. 339, Chicago, Illinois, effective April 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-1342. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1342, Bayou Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1953-1957 (Box 143, Folder 34)
      May 16, 1953-September 9, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 28, Houston, Texas, effective July 1, 1957
  - Sub-Series 235-1343. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1343, Milwaukee-Kansas City Southern Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1922-1955 (Box 143, Folder 35)
      September 13, 1922-March 10, 1955.
  - Sub-Series 235-1344. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1344, Grand Trunk Freight Handlers Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1926-1961 (Box 143, Folder 36)
      May 19, 1926-October 25, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 468, Chicago, Illinois, effective October 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1345. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1345, Golden Eagle Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1953-1963 (Box 143, Folder 37)
      June 1, 1953-April 4, 1963. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1102, Chicago, Illinois, effective January 1, 1963
    - Lodge No. 1345, Ohio Central Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1923-1931 (Box 143, Folder 37)
      December 19, 1923-August 13, 1931.
  - Sub-Series 235-1346. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1346, Pennsylvania Terminal Lodge, New York, New York, 1953-1962 (Box 143, Folder 38)
      August 3, 1953-June 8, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-1347. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1347, Henderson Lodge, Henderson, Kentucky, 1950-1951 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      July 12, 1950-July 1, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 407, Louisville, Kentucky, effective July 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-1349. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1349, Lackawanna Freight Handlers Lodge, New York, New York, 1921-1922 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      April 4, 1921-November 9, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1350. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1350, Lawton Lodge, Hutchinson, Kansas, 1930-1960 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      April 22, 1930-March 30, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1107, Liberal, Kansas, effective January 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1351. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1351, Passpa Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1953-1960 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      November 2, 1953-October 26, 1960.
    - Lodge No. 1351, Dorpian Lodge, Schenectady, New York, 1922-1923 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      March 22, 1922-October 29, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-1352. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1352, Station Employees Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1944-1960 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      February 9, 1944-March 24, 1960. Suspended, effective February, 1954
  - Sub-Series 235-1354. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1354, Tri-City Lodge, Oakland, California, 1954-1962 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      February 1, 1954-May 1, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1345, Chicago, Illinois, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1360. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1360, Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal Red Cap Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1954-1958 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      July 12, 1954-December 4, 1958.
    - Lodge No. 1360, Camden Lodge, Camden, New Jersey, 1929 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      February 20, 1929-April 25, 1929. Disbanded?
  - Sub-Series 235-1365. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1365, Seaway Lodge, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1955-1956 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      August 22, 1955-December 1, 1956. Disbanded, effective December 1, 1956
    - Lodge No. 1365, Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1922 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      April 27, 1922-May 12, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1367. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1367, Tri-State Lodge, Harlan, Kentucky, 1930-1969 (Box 144, Folder 10)
      April 10, 1930-March 7, 1969. Consolidated with Lodge No. 611, Corbin, Kentucky, effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1368. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1368, Wellington Lodge, Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, 1955-1957 (Box 144, Folder 11)
      October 10, 1955-January 25, 1957. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1956
    - Lodge No. 1368, Green Mountain Lodge, Bennington, Vermont, 1923 (Box 144, Folder 11)
      1923 December 4
  - Sub-Series 235-1369. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1369, Southern Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1955-1962 (Box 144, Folder 12)
      October 24, 1955-July 26, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 543, Dallas, Texas; Lodge No. 907, Ennis, Texas; and Lodge No. 1426, Fort Worth, Texas; effective July 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1370. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1370, Tillicum Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1955-1968 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      November 21, 1955-October 22, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1321, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, effective April 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 1370, Cresson Lodge, Cresson, Pennsylvania, 1923 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      May 14-18, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-1375. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1375, Desert View Lodge, Yuma, Arizona, 1960 (Box 144, Folder 14)
      April 4, 1960-December 5, 1960. Subject: Appeal Decision of the Grand President that the vote cast in the election of Division Chairman by Brother John A. Jung, was invalid, that the election resulted in a tie vote, and that the contest should be determined by the System Board of Adjustment as provided in Article 1, Section 6, of the Protective Laws"
  - Sub-Series 235-1377. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1377, Rock Island Lodge, Topeka, Kansas, 1921-1960 (Box 144, Folder 15)
      June 11, 1921-November 29, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 150, Herington, Kansas, effective January 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1381. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1381, Winston Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1956-1963 (Box 144, Folder 16)
      March 19, 1956-November 29, 1963. Consolidated with Lodge No. 725, Cleveland, Ohio, effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1382. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1382, Penn Center Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1956-1960 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      April 9, 1956-April 21, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6329, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, effective April 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1387. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1387, East Coast Lodge, St. Augustine, Florida, 1957-1958 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      March 11, 1957-October 6, 1958. Consolidated with Lodge No. 848, St. Augustine, Florida, effective October 6, 1958
    - Lodge No. 1387, St. Thomas, Ontario, Canada, 1921 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      December 16-20, 1921.
  - Sub-Series 235-1389. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1389, Franklin D. Roosevelt Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1957-1964 (Box 144, Folder 19)
      December 11, 1957-January 9, 1964. Consolidated with Lodge No. 618, Chicago, Illinois, effective October 1, 1963
    - Lodge No. 1389, Pine Tree Lodge, Portland, Maine, 1929 (Box 144, Folder 19)
      October 8, 1929-November 5, 1929.
  - Sub-Series 235-1392. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1392, Caldwell Lodge, Princeton, Kentucky, 1930-1951 (Box 144, Folder 20)
      December 11, 1930-October 19, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 733, Paducah, Kentucky and Lodge No. 2055, Fulton, Kentucky, effective October 18, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-1394. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1394, Fortuna Lodge, Jackson, Michigan, 1928-1929 (Box 144, Folder 21)
      July 20, 1928-October 31, 1929.
    - Lodge No. 1394, Bellingham, Washington, 1922 (Box 144, Folder 21)
      February 7, 1922-March 21, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1395. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1395, Lindy Lodge, Owosso, Michigan, 1929-1932 (Box 144, Folder 22)
      December 28, 1929-March 15, 1932.
  - Sub-Series 235-1398. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1398, Gerber, California, 1930 (Box 144, Folder 23)
      1930 November 6
  - Sub-Series 235-1402. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1402, Cascade Lodge, Seattle, Washington, 1933-1930 (Box 144, Folder 24)
      April 20, 1933-May 23, 1930.
  - Sub-Series 235-1403. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1403, J. C. Boyer Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1923-1959 (Box 144, Folder 25)
      January 8, 1923-April 10, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-1404. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1404, Northern Pacific Mainstreeter Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1921-1962 (Box 144, Folder 26)
      April 25, 1921-Decmeber 19, 1962. Formerly Northern Pacific General Office Lodge
  - Sub-Series 235-1405. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1405, Central Inspection Bureau Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1928-1932 (Box 144, Folder 27)
      July 27, 1928-July 14, 1932.
  - Sub-Series 235-1406. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1406, Wausau, Wisconsin, 1950-1962 (Box 144, Folder 28)
      October 22, 1950-April 13, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1329, La Crosse, Wisconsin, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1407. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1407, Terminal Lodge, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 1921-1923 (Box 144, Folder 29)
      December 27, 1921-February 20, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-1408. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1408, Louisville Lodge, Louisville, Kentucky, 1921-1967 (Box 144, Folder 30)
      June 16, 1921-November 22, 1967. Formerly Southern Railway Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 1083, Cincinnati, Ohio, effective July 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1410. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1410, LaFayette Lodge, Fayetteville, North Carolina, 1921-1925 (Box 144, Folder 31)
      April 29, 1921-September 28, 1925.
  - Sub-Series 235-1412. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1412, Ellen Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1921-1959 (Box 144, Folder 32)
      September 6, 1921-March 2, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-1413. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1413, Lebanon, Kentucky, 1945-1955 (Box 144, Folder 33)
      December 3, 1945-June 9, 1955. Consolidated with Lodge No. 407, Louisville, Kentucky, effective April 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-1415. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1415, Mayo Lodge, Rochester, Minnesota, 1946-1960 (Box 144, Folder 34)
      May 23, 1946-November 28, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 129, Winona, Minnesota, and Lodge No. 2072, St. Paul, Minnesota, effective October 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1416. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1416, Kingston, Ontario, Canada, 1933-1954 (Box 144, Folder 35)
      April 21, 1933-October 1, 1954. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1161, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, effective October 1, 1954
  - Sub-Series 235-1419. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1419, Overland Lodge, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1922-1926 (Box 144, Folder 36)
      August 21, 1922-March 16, 1926. Formerly Weiser Lodge
  - Sub-Series 235-1421. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1421, Lawrence Lodge, Lawrence, Kansas, 1931-1962 (Box 144, Folder 37)
      October 17, 1931-April 13, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 51, Topeka, Kansas; Lodge No. 395, Salina, Kansas; and Lodge No. 1489, Kansas City, Missouri; effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1422. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1422, Harvey Wells Lodge, Wellston, Ohio, 1921-1922 (Box 144, Folder 38)
      July 20, 1921-April 6, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1423. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1423, Stamford Lodge, Stamford, Texas, 1922 (Box 144, Folder 39)
      February 7, 1922-March 1, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1424. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1424, Wheeling Terminal Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1928-1954 (Box 144, Folder 40)
      August 17, 1928-January 20, 1954. Consolidated with Lodge No. 234, Toledo, Ohio, effective December 1, 1953
  - Sub-Series 235-1425. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1425, Bristol, Tennessee, 1933 (Box 144, Folder 41)
      October 27, 1933-November 10, 1933.
  - Sub-Series 235-1427. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1427, Grand Trunk Lodge, South Bend, Indiana, 1926-1959 (Box 144, Folder 42)
      March 31, 1926-September 10, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 468, Chicago, Illinois, effective July 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-1429. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1429, Clinton, Illinois, 1930 (Box 144, Folder 43)
      February 3-11, 1930.
  - Sub-Series 235-1431. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1431, Arkansas-Louisiana Lodge, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1929-1961 (Box 144, Folder 44)
      June 28, 1929-January 12, 1961. Moved from Alexandria, Louisiana, and previously from New Orleans, Louisiana; consolidated with Lodge No. 1461, Shreveport, Louisiana, effective January 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1435. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1435, Anchorage Lodge, Anchorage, Alaska, 1928-1931 (Box 144, Folder 45)
      December 28, 1928-May 5, 1931.
  - Sub-Series 235-1436. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1436, Standard Lodge, Montgomery, Alabama, 1936-1960 (Box 144, Folder 46)
      January 30, 1936-January 7, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 539, Montgomery, Alabama; Lodge No. 957, Tuscaloosa, Alabama; and Lodge No. 1420, Wilmington, North Carolina; effective January 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 1436, Willow Lodge, Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada, 1921 (Box 144, Folder 46)
      February 20, 1921-March 11, 1921.
  - Sub-Series 235-1437. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1437, St. Louis, Missouri, 1921-1924 (Box 144, Folder 47)
      October 7, 1921-March 29, 1924.
  - Sub-Series 235-1438. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1438, Underwood Lodge, Greycourt, New York, 1922 (Box 144, Folder 48)
      January 20-27, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1441. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1441, New Butler Lodge, New Butler, Wisconsin, 1931 (Box 144, Folder 49)
      April 25, 1931-October 15, 1931.
  - Sub-Series 235-1442. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1442, Jewell Lodge, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1944-1963 (Box 144, Folder 50)
      July 22, 1944-August 2, 1963. Consolidated with Lodge No. 185, El Reno, Oklahoma, and Lodge No. 222, Shawnee, Oklahoma, effective July 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1444. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1444, Kent, Ohio, September 29, 1921 (Box 144, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 235-1445. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1445, Monon Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1929-1937 (Box 144, Folder 52)
      April 9, 1929-October 11, 1937. Consolidated with Lodge No. 709, Lafayette, Indiana, effective October 1, 1937
  - Sub-Series 235-1448. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1448, Worth Lodge, Fort Worth, Texas, 1923-1962 (Box 144, Folder 53)
      June 26, 1923-April 26, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 170, Waco, Texas, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1451. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1451, West Toronto Lodge, West Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1921-1961 (Box 144, Folder 54)
      February 12, 1921-April 20, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 951, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, effective March 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1452. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1452, Transcona Lodge, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1929-1933 (Box 144, Folder 55)
      October 30, 1929-January 26, 1933. Disbanded
  - Sub-Series 235-1455. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1455, Millerdale Lodge, Cumberland, Maryland, 1921-1923 (Box 144, Folder 56)
      October 13, 1921-March 28, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-1457. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1457, Twin City Lodge, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1921-1923 (Box 144, Folder 57)
      December 14, 1921-February 3, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-1460. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1460, Clover Leaf Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1929-1932 (Box 144, Folder 58)
      July 6, 1929-July 6, 1932.
  - Sub-Series 235-1464. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1464, Fort Worth, Texas, 1931-1932 (Box 144, Folder 59)
      July 31, 1931-October 21, 1932.
  - Sub-Series 235-1465. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1465, Charleston Lodge, Charleston, Illinois, 1930 (Box 144, Folder 60)
      April 22, 1930-May 6, 1930. Suspended, effective April 18, 1930
  - Sub-Series 235-1466. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1466, Osborn Lodge, Marion, Indiana, 1922-1923 (Box 144, Folder 61)
      January 23, 1922-February 5, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-1467. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1467, Marion, Indiana, 1930 (Box 144, Folder 62)
      June 4, 1930-July 31, 1930.
    - Lodge No. 1467, Old Reliable Lodge, Augusta, Georgia, 1921 (Box 144, Folder 62)
      December 2-12, 1921.
  - Sub-Series 235-1471. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1471, Durango Lodge, Durango, Colorado, 1925-1957 (Box 144, Folder 63)
      January 30, 1925-July 24, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 663, Grand Junction, Colorado, July 1, 1957
  - Sub-Series 235-1472. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1472, Joffre Lodge, Quebec, Quebec, Canada, 1921-1922 (Box 144, Folder 64)
      April 11, 1921-October 20, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1473. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1473, Smiths Falls, Ontario, Canada, 1930 (Box 144, Folder 65)
      1930 May 3
  - Sub-Series 235-1474. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1474, Commerce, Texas, 1954-1960 (Box 144, Folder 66)
      May 20, 1954-November 21, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 543, Dallas, Texas, effective October 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1476. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1476, Amory Lodge, Amory, Mississippi, 1934-1962 (Box 144, Folder 67)
      May 2, 1934-December 4, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-1477. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1477, Queen City Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1921-1923 (Box 144, Folder 68)
      May 10, 1921-January 24, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-1482. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1482, Pekin, Illinois, 1930 (Box 144, Folder 69)
      1930 May 9
    - Lodge No. 1482, Cayuga Lodge, Auburn, New York, 1921 (Box 144, Folder 69)
      August 17-23, 1921.
  - Sub-Series 235-1483. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1483, Wicomico Lodge, Salisbury, Maryland, 1922 (Box 144, Folder 70)
      July 24, 1922-September 13, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1486. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1486, Wayburn, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1921-1955 (Box 145, Folder 1)